<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
  <element name="Lustful Caress" type="Feat" source="Me, myself and I" id="ID_XENIRATH_FEAT_LUSTFUL_CARESS">
    <supports />
		<prerequisite>Tiefling, Charisma 16 or higher.</prerequisite>
		<requirements>ID_RACE_TIEFLING, [cha:16]</requirements>
    <description>
      <p><i>Prerequisites: Tiefling, Charisma 16 or higher.</i></p>
      <p>After sensing your fiendish lineage pulse with dark power years ago, you've been training in the magic of lust. 
	  By touching someone with a tiny bit of your saliva, sweat or cum, you can use an action to attempt to seduce them, increasing their libido and deeply charming them for a duration of your concentration (max 1 hour). </p>
	  <ul>
	  <li>The creature must have an intelligence of 5 or more, and must make a wisdom saving throw against your spell DC (8 + prof + cha mod). </li>
	  <li>If the creature saves, the creature becomes immune to this charm for the next 24 hours. </li>
	  <li>If the creature fails, they become charmed and are deeply seduced for an hour; if the target receives damage directed from someone outside the party and allies, the target gets to save again.</li> 
	  <li>Also, if the caster does something bad or trully harmful to them (safe BDSM doesn't count), or the caster loses concentration or becomes unconscious, then the spell instantly ends.</li>
	  
	  The caster can end the spell as a bonus action. Only one creature can be affected by the charm at a time, and if the spell is cast or affects another creature, the first creature will stop being affected. 
	  When the spell ends, the affected creature realizes magic was used on them, but if treated well during the spell, they might not be hostile or even angry about it.
	  </ul>
	  
	  <p>While concentrating on the spell, the effect on a creature can be reinforced without ending it. To do so, you must reapply the saliva and use another use of this feature, and the target must make a wisdom saving throw with disadvantage against your spell dc. If they fail, the charm's time (an hour) is reset. If they succeed, the spell ends, wasting that use.
	  You can use this feature an amount of times equal to your CHAmod per short or long rest.</p>    
    </description>
    <setters>
      <set name="sourceUrl"> </set>
    </setters>
        <sheet>
            <description> You gain the ability to deeply seduce a creature. </description>
        </sheet>
  </element>
</elements>